

KONSTANTIN MISHIN

STUDENT AT
EESTI ETTEVÕTLUSKÕRGKOOL MAINOR
TALLINN, HARJUMAA, ESTONIA

Contact

Personal Portfolio/Resume Website: https://oaf131.github.io/konstantin-mishin.dev

Email:

konstantin.webdev.01@gmail.com

Linkedin Profile:

linkedin.com/in/konstantin-mishin-webdev

Profile

Highly motivated third-year student at Eesti Ettevõtluskõrgkooli Mainor, pursuing a Bachelor's degree in Web Technologies, passionate about web development and related fields. Open to opportunities that provide practical experience and professional growth, with the goal of becoming a skilled and sought-after specialist in the industry!

Education

2022 - Present

Estonian Entrepreneurship
University of Applied Sciences / EEK
Mainor

Bachelor's Degree in Web Technologies (In Progress)

Job Experience

April 2024 - Present

Self Employed

I undertake a variety of part-time jobs and temporary assignments that require versatility, flexibility, responsibility, and effective client interaction

October 2023 - April 2024

Electrician

ELCITY OÜ

Installation, Maintenance, and Troubleshooting of Power and Low-Voltage Electrical Networks

Skills

- Frontend Development: HTML, CSS, Bootstarp
- Backend Development: Node.js, PHP, Python
- Cross-Platform Development: Flutter (Dart)
- Database Management: Building and managing databases with Oracle, MySQL, and Firebase
- UI/UX Design: User Research, Prototyping and Wireframing (Figma, Adobe XD), Responsive design

Interests

■ Hiking ■ Philosophy ■ Books ■ Movies